Hi, everybody, my name is Peter.
Ah... otherwise known as Britjet on PSX forums.
I'm a retired BA(British Airways) 747 pilot and ...
playing with PSX
but I am not sure that's the right word, because it's so realistic.
certainly got me hooked.
And I thought I put together, some videos
showing some aspects of the operation
the 747 which might not be immediately obvious
in various manuals you can get you hands on.
Health warning:
any pros watching this trying to glean some information
for your next check
Please don't, just use your own SOPs and your knowledges
I'm sure it's equally as good as mine if not much better
This is just for fun, OK?
This particular approach is, e...
onto 27L Heathrow.
all LOC on
And ATCs are gonna tell us or ask us
to go for 27R.
There are also some bottom lines to this
Don't do it in bad weather.
you couldn't be able to see the other runway
And don't trying do this below 2000ft